[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 8, "question": "Did the president call?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "the", "president", "call", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 9, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "What do they need from somebody like you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "they", "need", "from", "somebody", "like", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Well, they all have something different.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "they", "all", "have", "something", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 48, "question": "When that specific thing is happening, what do you say?", "question_tokens": ["When", "that", "specific", "thing", "is", "happening", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 49, "answer": "It's not a say, it's putting him back in state.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "say", ",", "it", "'s", "putting", "him", "back", "in", "state", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "I mean despite all these incredible things that you've experienced, to have the president of your country call you in his great hour of need?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "despite", "all", "these", "incredible", "things", "that", "you", "'ve", "experienced", ",", "to", "have", "the", "president", "of", "your", "country", "call", "you", "in", "his", "great", "hour", "of", "need", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Well, you know, if you're thinking about yourself in a moment like that, you can't really serve, so then it would be all about you.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "if", "you", "'re", "thinking", "about", "yourself", "in", "a", "moment", "like", "that", ",", "you", "ca", "n't", "really", "serve", ",", "so", "then", "it", "would", "be", "all", "about", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Do you personally ever have crushing moments of self-doubt?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "personally", "ever", "have", "crushing", "moments", "of", "self-doubt", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "Self-doubt as often as you do.", "answer_tokens": ["Self-doubt", "as", "often", "as", "you", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Now be honest, when you first heard that, what was your reaction?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "be", "honest", ",", "when", "you", "first", "heard", "that", ",", "what", "was", "your", "reaction", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "That was pretty horrific.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "was", "pretty", "horrific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "How helpful is that to exuding the kinds of inner self-belief that you clearly have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "helpful", "is", "that", "to", "exuding", "the", "kinds", "of", "inner", "self-belief", "that", "you", "clearly", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, clearly it's not just about inner self-belief, it's really about people getting to the truth.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "clearly", "it", "'s", "not", "just", "about", "inner", "self-belief", ",", "it", "'s", "really", "about", "people", "getting", "to", "the", "truth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "Did she ever tell you she loved you?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "ever", "tell", "you", "she", "loved", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "Absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 159, "question": "OK?", "question_tokens": ["OK", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 160, "answer": "Sounds like perfect.", "answer_tokens": ["Sounds", "like", "perfect", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 239, "question": "What does he need?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "he", "need", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 240, "answer": "I'm a strategist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "strategist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "In one minute or two?", "question_tokens": ["In", "one", "minute", "or", "two", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "CD", "NN", "CC", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "What's the last one of your five points?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "the", "last", "one", "of", "your", "five", "points", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "It's the health side.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "the", "health", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 341, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 342, "answer": "I love the way you were laughing so uncomfortably at yourself dancing there.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "the", "way", "you", "were", "laughing", "so", "uncomfortably", "at", "yourself", "dancing", "there", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "Well, I mean, could you imagine if you were dancing like that?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "could", "you", "imagine", "if", "you", "were", "dancing", "like", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Oh, it is?", "question_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Pretty much, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Pretty", "much", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Do you still look on scenes like that with great affection or does it become this terrible curse you wish you'd ever been involved with?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "still", "look", "on", "scenes", "like", "that", "with", "great", "affection", "or", "does", "it", "become", "this", "terrible", "curse", "you", "wish", "you", "'d", "ever", "been", "involved", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Hardly.", "answer_tokens": ["Hardly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "\"Seinfeld\"?", "question_tokens": ["``", "Seinfeld", "''", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["``", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "TO", "WRB", "JJ", ":", "RB", "TO", "WRB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 367, "question": "At moment when you first start making (INAUDIBLE), at what moment do you start thinking -- actually this could be huge?", "question_tokens": ["At", "moment", "when", "you", "first", "start", "making", "(", "INAUDIBLE", ")", ",", "at", "what", "moment", "do", "you", "start", "thinking", "--", "actually", "this", "could", "be", "huge", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ":", "RB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 368, "answer": "I think I never really caught up to how big -- honestly to how big it was until right before we ended.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "I", "never", "really", "caught", "up", "to", "how", "big", "--", "honestly", "to", "how", "big", "it", "was", "until", "right", "before", "we", "ended", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "I swear to you.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "swear", "to", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Didn't like 100 million people watch that?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "n't", "like", "100", "million", "people", "watch", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "VB", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I don't remember.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "remember", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "It was like a Super Bowl, yes.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "like", "a", "Super", "Bowl", ",", "yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "Do we have a fact checker here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "we", "have", "a", "fact", "checker", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "If I'm exaggerating, go with me.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "I", "'m", "exaggerating", ",", "go", "with", "me", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 403, "question": "Do you have like little \"Seinfeld\" reunions in some dingy little bar in Manhattan?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "like", "little", "``", "Seinfeld", "''", "reunions", "in", "some", "dingy", "little", "bar", "in", "Manhattan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "``", "NNP", "''", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 404, "answer": "We get together on a daily basis.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "get", "together", "on", "a", "daily", "basis", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Manhattan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 408, "question": "Do the ships just pass out of the port and that's it?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "the", "ships", "just", "pass", "out", "of", "the", "port", "and", "that", "'s", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 409, "answer": "We do see each other on occasion.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "do", "see", "each", "other", "on", "occasion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 423, "question": "What is it about that show, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "that", "show", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 424, "answer": "Well, I think it's a couple things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "a", "couple", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 515, "question": "Don't you have a bleeper here?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "n't", "you", "have", "a", "bleeper", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 516, "answer": "Yes, we're going to have to now.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "we", "'re", "going", "to", "have", "to", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Did you have more or less sympathy for her by the end of your process, just on what it takes to be a vice president?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "have", "more", "or", "less", "sympathy", "for", "her", "by", "the", "end", "of", "your", "process", ",", "just", "on", "what", "it", "takes", "to", "be", "a", "vice", "president", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "CC", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "RB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I have more sympathy for all women in government.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "more", "sympathy", "for", "all", "women", "in", "government", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palins"]}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RBR", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 535, "question": "More Sarah Palins?", "question_tokens": ["More", "Sarah", "Palins", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["JJR", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 536, "answer": "No, not more Sarah Palins in my opinion.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "more", "Sarah", "Palins", "in", "my", "opinion", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sarah Palins"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ":", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", ":"], "qSentId": 548, "question": "No, I mean just generally for women in America right now?", "question_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "mean", "just", "generally", "for", "women", "in", "America", "right", "now", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 549, "answer": "Well, it's interesting because all of these issues are -- trans-vaginal probes and --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "because", "all", "of", "these", "issues", "are", "--", "trans-vaginal", "probes", "and", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Are you expecting some sharp flip-flopping?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "expecting", "some", "sharp", "flip-flopping", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "I know.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "know", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "What do you make of your country right now generally?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "your", "country", "right", "now", "generally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "I love it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "love", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 593, "question": "What is the solution for America?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "the", "solution", "for", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 594, "answer": "I have no idea.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "no", "idea", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 600, "question": "How are we going to get there?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "we", "going", "to", "get", "there", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 601, "answer": "For my children, I want my children to be active.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "my", "children", ",", "I", "want", "my", "children", "to", "be", "active", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 606, "question": "What else?", "question_tokens": ["What", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 607, "answer": "That's good.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 615, "question": "You do?", "question_tokens": ["You", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 616, "answer": "Yes, it's why you should be running for office.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "it", "'s", "why", "you", "should", "be", "running", "for", "office", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "What office do you think I should run for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "office", "do", "you", "think", "I", "should", "run", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "I would go on the anti-transvaginal probe brigade.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "go", "on", "the", "anti-transvaginal", "probe", "brigade", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 652, "question": "What part of that character did he fall in love with?", "question_tokens": ["What", "part", "of", "that", "character", "did", "he", "fall", "in", "love", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 653, "answer": "I'm not sure any part of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "any", "part", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Yeah, you think?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", ",", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Yes, definitely.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "definitely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 674, "question": "How have the pair of you, who are in the same profession, managed to stay happily married for 25 years?", "question_tokens": ["How", "have", "the", "pair", "of", "you", ",", "who", "are", "in", "the", "same", "profession", ",", "managed", "to", "stay", "happily", "married", "for", "25", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 675, "answer": "Well, let's see, first of all, we're separating.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "'s", "see", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "we", "'re", "separating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "How did you know he was the right guy?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "know", "he", "was", "the", "right", "guy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Here's the deal.", "answer_tokens": ["Here", "'s", "the", "deal", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Do you feel lucky?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "lucky", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "I do feel lucky.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "feel", "lucky", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "Do you make each other laugh?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "make", "each", "other", "laugh", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "Oh, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Because there's an \"SNL\" battle every day?", "question_tokens": ["Because", "there", "'s", "an", "``", "SNL", "''", "battle", "every", "day", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "``", "NNP", "''", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "No, it's not an \"SNL\" battle.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "an", "``", "SNL", "''", "battle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 715, "question": "Are you seriously about to split up?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "seriously", "about", "to", "split", "up", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 716, "answer": "No, I'm kidding.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "'m", "kidding", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120505pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 730, "question": "What could go wrong?", "question_tokens": ["What", "could", "go", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 731, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]